Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Addenda / Exhibition Materials, / Date(s): 1920ca.-1997; Folder: A005; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <76x55cm. / Medium: Photographs / Support: Paper
Rockefeller Institute (Client) / Landscaping plans 0424
Rockefeller University / Landscaping plans 0424
Rockefeller University (Client) / Landscaping plans 0613, 0883, 0931
Rock Valley College (Client) / Landscaping plans 0722
Rohn and Haas Company (Client) / Landscaping plans 0500
Royal Bank of Calgary (Client) / Site plans 0738
Rutgers University (Client) / Master plans 0486
S&S (Architects) / Landscaping plans 0527
S & S Architects (Associated Architects) / Working drawings 0535
Saarinen & Associates (Architects) / Landscaping plans 0608
Saarinen & Associates (Architects) / Master plans 0398
Saks Center / Landscaping plans 05034
San Antonio Museum of Art (Client) / Master plans 01049
Sasaki, Dawson and Demay (Associated Landscape Architects) / Site plans 0872
Shelburne Museum (Client) / Landscaping plans 01053
Sherway Gardens / Landscaping plans 01276
Ships of the Sea Maritime Museum (Owner) / Landscaping plans 01028
Shorenstein Properties LLC (Client) / Landscaping plans 01167
Sir Winston Churchill Square / Landscaping plans 0714
Skidmore,Owings & Merrill (Architects) / Master plans 01206
Skidmore, Owings & Merrill (Architects) / Landscaping plans 01266
Skidmore Owings & Merrill (Architects) / Landscaping plans 01054, 0415
Skidmore Owings & Merrill (Architects) / Plans (Drawings) 01093
Skidmore Owings & Merrill (Architects) (Museum) / Plans (Drawings) 01093
Skidmore Owings & Merrill (Associated Architects) / Site plans 0528
Skidmore Owings and Merrill (Architects) / Master plans 0586
Skidmore Owings and Merrill (Architects) / Site plans 0421, 0422
Skidmore Owings and Merrill Architects) / Landscaping plans 0693
Smith & Smith (Landscape Architects) / Landscaping plans 01079
Smithsonian Institution (Client) / Landscaping plans 0953
Smokey House Center (Donor) / Planting plans 0459
Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort / Landscaping plans 0671
Sol y Nieve Ski Resort (Client) / Site plans 0969
Squibb-Beech-nut (Client) / Landscaping plans 0860
St. John's Seminary (Client) / Landscaping plans 01109
St. Louis Community College (Client) / Landscaping plans 0612
St. Paul's School (Client) / Master plans 0614
Standard and Chartered Banking Group (Client) / Landscaping plans 01018
State University of New York. College of Environmental Science and Forestry (Client) / Landscaping plans 0582
State University of New York at Buffalo (Client) / Landscaping plans 0839, 0840, 0904
StateUniversityof New York at Fredonia (Client) / Landscaping plans 0599
State University of New York at Fredonia (Client) / Landscaping plans 0600, 0601, 0634, 0635
State University of New York at Fredonia (Client) / Master plans 0570
State University of New York at Fredonia (Client) / Site plans 05026
State University of New York at Fredonia (Clients) / Landscaping plans 0881
State University of New York at Potsdam (Client) / Landscaping plans 0555, 0729, 0759
State University of New York at Potsdam (Client) / Site plans 05027
State University of New York at Purchase (Client) / Landscaping plans 01089
State University of New York at Stony Brook (Client) / Landscaping plans 0886
Stone & Webster (Client) / Landscaping plans 0947
Stull and Lee, Inc. (Architects) / Landscaping plans 0917
Sugarloaf Farms (Client) / Master plans 0905
Sugarloaf Inn (Client) / Landscaping plans 0481
Sugarloaf Mountain Ski Lodge (Client) / Landscaping plans 0445
Texas Research Park / Landscaping plans 05038
Thrall Car Manufacturing Company (Client) / Landscaping plans 0663
Topnotch (Resort) (Client) / Landscaping plans 01071
Trapp Family Singers (Clients) / Plans (Drawings) 01014
Trinity College (Client) / Landscaping plans 01072
Tufts University (Client) / Landscaping plans 0775, 0788
Tufts University (Client) / Master plans 0861
Tufts University (Client) / Site plans 0692, 0741
Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation (Client) / Preliminary drawings 01258
Twin Farms (Client) / Landscaping plans 01259
U.S. Department of the Interior. Bureau of Indian Affairs (Client) / Site plans 0942
Union Carbide Corporation (Client) / Site plans 0421
United Engineers & Contructors, Inc. (Client) / Landscaping plans 0946
United States. Department of State (Client) / Competition drawings 01112
United States. Federal Aviation Administration (Client) / Landscaping plans 0597
United States. Federal Bureau of Investigation (Client) / Planting plans 0744
United States. General Services Administration / Landscaping plans 01210
United States. General Services Administration / Master plans 01171
United States. National Park Service / Landscaping plans 0457
United States. Office of Strategic Services. Presentation Branch. / Architectural drawings 0048
United States. Public Buildings Administration (Client) / Site plans 0042
United States Air Force Academy (Client) / Landscaping plans 0415
United States Air Force Academy (Client) / Landscaping plans 0718
United States Housing Authority (Client) / Landscaping plans 0239
Universal North (Client) / Preliminary drawings 01228
University of California at Santa Cruz (Client) / Landscaping plans 0754
University of Chicago (Client) / Landscapinge plans 05036
University of Chicago (Client) / Landscaping plans 0451, 0693
University of Lagos (Client) / Planting plans 0694
University of Massachusetts (UMass) / Site plans 05024
University of Minnesota (Client) / Landscaping plans 0619, 0621
University of Ottawa / Landscaping plans 01280
University of Pennsylvania / Landscaping plans 0831
University of Pennsylvania (Client) / Landscaping plans 0441
University of Vermont (Client) / Landscaping plans 0553, 0617, 0650, 0795, 0803
University of Vermont (Client) / Master plans 0583, 0807, 0985
University of Vermont (Client) / Site plans 0701, 0702
University of Wisconsin (Client) / Landscaping plans 0724
Urban Retail Properties (Developer) / Landscaping plans 0922
Vanderbilt University (Client) / Master plans 01100
Vero Beach & Polo Club / Landscaping plans 01248
Vertue Ariel (Sailboat) / Architectural drawings 05040
Voorsanger & Mills Associates (Architects) / Landscaping plans 01191
Wadsworth Atheneum (Client) / Master plans 0806
Walk Jones & Francis Mah (Architects) / Landscaping plans 01060, 01065
Warner Burns Toan & Lundy (Architects) [?] / Landscaping plans 0910
Washington, D.C. (Client) / Landscaping plans 0689, 0690
Washington International University (Client) / Master plans 01232
Weese, Harry & Associates (Architect) / Master plans 0715
Welton Becket and Associates (Architects) / Landscaping plans 0946, 0947
Westchester County (N.Y.) Dept. of Parks, Recreation & Conservation / Topographic maps 01004
White Mountain Development / Landscaping plans 0534
White Mountain National Forest / Landscaping plans 0534
Williams College (Client) / Site plans 0757
Williams College [?] (client [?] / Site plans 0848
Winooski (Vt.). Client / Municipal plans 01011
Winooski (Vt.) (Client) / Municipal plans 01010
Wolf Trap Foundation for Performing Arts (Client) / Site plans 0709
Wrexham Trust (Client) / Landscaping plans 0541
Xerox Corporation (Client) / Site plans 0814
Yale University / Landscaping plans 0541
Yale University. Jonathan Edwards College / Landscaping plans 0678
Yale University (Client) / Landscaping plans 0678
Yale University (Client) / Master plans 0487
YWCA of Minneapolis (Client) / Landscaping plans 0853
Zeidler Roberts Partnership (Archtects) / Landscaping plans 01276
Conference Names Index
Olympic Games (23rd: 1984: Los Angeles, CA) / Landscaping plans 05030
Titles Index
"Nuclear Energy" / Landscaping plans 0693
General Plan of Franklin Park / Site plans 0730
Willard Basin Ski Development / Landscaping plans 05042
LC Topical Headings Index
Architectural offices / Surveys 05003
Architecture, Domestic--California--Hollywood / Sketches 01283
Blackouts in war / Architectural drawings 0043
Civil defense--United States / Architectural drawings 0043
Deaf college students--United States / Master plans 0992
Deaf--Education / Master plans 0992
Indians of North America--Education / Site plans 0942
Landscape architects--Homes and haunts / Plans (Drawings) 05004
Landscape architects--Homes and Haunts / Surveys 05003
Nuremberg Trial of Major German War Criminals, Nuremberg, Germany, 1945-1946 / Architectural drawings 0048
Nuremberg War Crimes Trials, Nuremberg, Germany, 1946-1949 / Architectural drawings 0048
Rice and rice culture -- South Carolina / Landscaping plans 0932
Sailboats--Design and construction / Architectural drawings 05040
Geographic Names Index
[Vermont?}: ?; 8 Bells Farm / Landscape plans 0989
Bahamas: Great Guana Cay: Orchid Bay [?} / Landscaping plans 05028
Barbados, B.W.I.: St. Joseph: Easy Hall / Landscaping plans 01209
Belgium: Brussels: AG Group Headquarters / Landscaping plans 01213
Belgium: Brussels: Cummins Engine Company / Planting plans 0998
Belgium: Machelen: Rotunda Park Machelen / Landscaping plans 01230
California: Brentwood: Norman Lear Residence / Landscaping plans 01239
California: Century City / Preliminary drawings 01238
California: Los Angeles: 1801 Angelo Drive / Sketches 01283
California: Los Angeles: 818 Block / Master plans 01255
California: Los Angeles: 818 Block: Macklowe Bldg. / Master plans 01256
California: Los Angeles: 818 Seventh Street / Master plans 01254
California: Los Angeles: Ahmanson Building / Master plans 01254
California: Los Angeles: Barker Brothers (Firm) / Master plans 01254
California: Los Angeles: Eighth Street / Master plans 01254, 01255
California: Los Angeles: Figueroa Street / Master plans 01254, 01255
California: Los Angeles: Flower Street / Master plans 01254
California: Los Angeles: Geffen Residence / Sketches 01283
California: Los Angeles: Halekulani Hotel / Master plans 01255
California: Los Angeles: Olympic Village Site / Landscaping plans 05030
California: Los Angeles: Seventh Street / Master plans 01255
California: Los Angeles: Shorenstein Projects / Landscaping plans 01167
California: Los Angles: Twentierth Century-Fox Film Corporation / Preliminary drawings 01258
California: Novato: Buck Center on Aging / Landscaping plans 01221
California: Oakland: Oakland Museum / Planting plans 0536
California: Sacramento: Capitol Redevelopment Competition / Competition drawings 01223
California: San Francisco: Candlestick Point Park / Landscaping plans 01079
California: San Francisco: Shorenstein Projects / Landscaping plans 01167
California: San Jose: Silicon Valley Financial Center / Plans (Drawings) 01093
California: Santa: Cruz: University of California at Santa Cruz / Landscaping plans 0754
California: Woodside: Jobs Residence / Landscaping plans 01126
Canada: Calgary: Calgary Place / Site plans 0738
Canada: Calgary: Pacific 66 Plaza / Landscaping plans 0766
Canada: Calgary: Pacific Petroleums, Ltd. / Landscaping plans 0766
Canada: Calgary: Palliser Square / Site plans 0738
Canada: Edmonton: Sir Winston Churchill Square / Landscaping plans 0714
Canada: Kitimat, B.C.: Alcan City / Master plans 0216
Canada: Montreal: International Civil Aviation Organization Headquarters (Former) / Architectural drawings 0849
Canada: Montreal: Turner Residence / Sketches 01226
Canada: Ottawa: University of Ottawa / Landscaping plans 01280
Canada: Quebec: Montreal / Landscaping plans 0945
Canada: Senneville: Ball Residence / Landscaping plans 01174
Canada: Ste. Agathe: David Culver Residence / Landscaping plans 01199
Canada: Toronto / Site plans 0876
Canada: Toronto: David Thomson Residence / Landscaping plans 01250
Canada: Toronto: Sherway Gardens / Landscaping plans 01276
Colorado: Carbondale: Colorado Rocky Mountain School / Landscaping plans 01073
Colorado: Colorado Springs: United States Air Force Academy / Landscaping plans 0415
Colorado: Colorado Springs: United States Air Force Academy / Landscaping plans 0718
Colorado: Loveland: Bierwaltes Residence / Preliminary drawings 01277
Colorado: Snowmass / Landscaping plans 0858
Colorado: Vail: Arrowhead / Site plans 01024
Connecticut: Greenwch: Louis Baker Residence / Landscaping plans 0185
Connecticut: Hartford: Burr McManus Memorial Park / Landscaping plans 0547
Connecticut: Hartford: Wadsworth Atheneum Garden / Master plans 0806
Connecticut: Litchfield: Connecticut Junior Republic / Landscaping plans 0476
Connecticut: Newhallville: King/Robinson Inter-District Magnet School[?] / Landscaping plans 0917
Connecticut: Newhallville: Newhallville School / Landscaping plans 0917
Connecticut: New Haven: 460 Lexington Street / Landscaping plans 0537
Connecticut: New Haven: Black Rock Park / Landscaping plans 0721
Connecticut: New Haven: East Rock Park / Site plans 0746
Connecticut: New Haven: East Shore Park / Landscaping plans 0681, 0721
Connecticut: New Haven: East Shore Park / Master plans 01025
Connecticut: New Haven: Edgerton Park / Landscaping plans 0682
Connecticut: New Haven: Edgewood Park / Landscaping plans 0625
Connecticut: New Haven: Elm Street / Landscaping plans 0541
Connecticut: New Haven: Five Mile Point Light / Landscaping plans 0723
Connecticut: New Haven: Fort Nathan Hale / Landscaping plans 0721
Connecticut: New Haven: Grand Avenue Park: Bathhouse / Landscaping plans 0800
Connecticut: New Haven: Lenzi Park / Landscaping plans 0726
Connecticut: New Haven: Lighthouse Point Park / Landscaping plans 0684
Connecticut: New Haven: Lighthouse Point Park: Parking lot / Site plans 0773
Connecticut: New Haven: Long Island Sound / Site plans 0746
Connecticut: New Haven:New Haven Harbor / Landscaping plans 0681
Connecticut: New Haven: New Haven Harbor / Landscaping plans 0684
Connecticut: New Haven: New Haven Harbor / Site plans 0773
Connecticut: New Haven: Quinnipiac School / Landscaping plans 0537
Connecticut: New Haven: Rowing Channel / Site plans 0852
Connecticut: New Haven: Southwest Ledge Light / Landscaping plans 0723
Connecticut: New Haven: West River / Landscaping plans 0625
Connecticut: New Haven: West River Memorial Park / Landscaping plans 0625
Connecticut: New Haven: West Rock Park / Landscaping plans 0686
Connecticut: New Haven: Wooster Square (Neighborhood) / Landscaping plans 0725
Connecticut: New Haven: Wooster Street Playground / Landscaping plans 0725
Connecticut: New Haven: Yale University: Jonathan Edwards College / Landscaping plans 0678
Connecticut: Stamford: Fine Residence / Landscaping plans 0172
Connecticut: Stonington: Elliott Residence / Landscaping plans 01127
Connecticut: Westport: Saltzman Residence / Landscaping plans 01296
Connecticut: Wilton: Richardson-Vick, Inc. / Landscaping plans 0889
Delaware: Wilmington: Sinness Residence / Landscaping plans 0809
England: Chichester: Kevin Dash Residence / Sketches 01240
England: London: Crutched Friars / Landscaping plans 01057
England: London: London Standard Chartered Bank / Landscaping plans 01018
England: London: PA Melbourn Property / Landscaping plans 01249
England: Sedgewick: Gardiner's Corner / Landscaping plans 01042
England: West Stoke: Kevin Dash Residence / Sketches 01240
Florida: Boca Raton: Hamilton Residence / Landscaping plans 01027
Florida: Broward County: Floating City / Master plans 0816
Florida: Celebration: Disney Enterprises / Architect's drawings 01260
Florida: Cocoanut Grove: Field Residence / Schematic drawings 01039
Florida: Hallandale: Gulfstream Park / Landscaping plans 01155
Florida: Miami: Brickell Avenue / Landscaping plans 01164
Florida: Miami: Julia Field Residence / Landscaping plans 01231
Florida: Sarasota: Ringling Museum of Art / Master plans 0961
Florida: Tampa: NCNB Plaza / Preliminary drawings 01095
Florida: Tampa: Tampa Palms Office Building / Landscaping plans 01178
Florida: West Palm Beach: Waterfront / Landscaping plans 01297
Florida: Windsor: Vero Beach & Polo Club / Landscaping plans 01248
France:: Paris: Nanterre / Landscaping plans 0885
France: Paris: Dalle Centrale de la Defense / Landscaping plans 0885
France: Paris: La Defense / Landscaping plans 0885
Georgia; Atlanta: Woodruff Plaza / Landscaping plans 0962
Georgia: Atlanta: Coca-Cola Company / Master plans 0959
Georgia: Atlanta: North Avenue and Luckie St. / Master plans 0959
Georgia: Atlanta: Piedmont Park / Landscaping plans 0506
Georgia: Savannah: Scarborough House / Landscaping plans 01028
Georgia: Savannah: West Broad Street Negro School / Landscaping plans 01028
Germany: Nuremberg: Nuremberg Courthouse / Architectural drawings 0048
Guam: Agana: Legislature Building / Landscaping plans 01253
Ilinois: Chicago: Navy Pier Reconstruction / Landscaping plans 01273
Illinois:Chicago: Art Institute / Landscaping plans 0546
Illinois: Chicago: Central District Filtration Plant / Landscaping plans 0589
Illinois: Chicago: Chicago Teachers Union (Apartments) / Landscaping plans 0656
Illinois: Chicago: Grant Park / Landscaping plans 0563
Illinois: Chicago: Kenwod Housing / Site plans 0666
Illinois: Chicago: Lake Michigan / Master plans 01119
Illinois: Chicago: Lakeshore Park / Master plans 01119
Illinois: Chicago: Michigan Avenue / Landscaping plans 0546, 0636
Illinois: Chicago: One Hundred North Wacker Drive / Landscaping plans 01224
Illinois: Chicago: Regional Parks / Comprehensive plans 0717
Illinois: Chicago: Spielman Residence / Landscaping plans 01166
Illinois: Chicago: S-SW Interchange / Landscaping plans 0675
Illinois: Chicago: University of Chicago: Fermi Memorial / Landscaping plans 0693
Illinois: Chicago: University of Chicago: Regenstein Library / Landscaping plans 0693
Illinois: Chicago: University of Chicago: Women's Residence Hall / Landscapinge plans 05036
Illinois: Chicago: University of Chicago Law School / Landscaping plans 0451
Illinois: Chicago: Water Tower Place / Landscaping plans 0922
Illinois: Chicago Heights: Thrall Car Manufacturing Company / Landscaping plans 0663
Illinois: Rockford: Rock Valley College / Landscaping plans 0722
Indiana: Charlestown: Cummins Engine Company / Landscaping plans 0936
Indiana: Columbus: Bartholomew County Courthouse / Landscaping plans 0906
Indiana: Columbus: Central Junior High School / Site plans 0591
Indiana: Columbus: Clarence Hamilton Residence / Landscaping plans 0573
Indiana: Columbus: Columbus Country Club / Site plans 0593
Indiana: Columbus: Columbus Senior High School / Site plans 0591
Indiana: Columbus: Community Schools / Site plans 0591
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Co./Main Plant / Landscaping plans 01001
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company / Landscaping plans 0508
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company: Creamery / Landscaping plans 05032
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company:Fabrication Facility / Site plan 0937
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company: Fabrication Facility / Site plan 0937
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company: Fleetguard Expansion / Landscaping plans 0719
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company: Storage Facility / Landscaping plans 0934
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Engine Company: Warehouse / Landscaping plans 0720
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Plant #1 / Landscaping plans 01001
Indiana: Columbus: Cummins Research Laboratory / Landscaping plans 0594
Indiana: Columbus: First Baptist Church / Landscaping plans 0657
Indiana: Columbus: George Newlin Residence / Landscaping plans 0575
Indiana: Columbus: Hamilton-Cosco Company / Landscaping plans 0539
Indiana: Columbus: Indiana Bell Telephone / Landscaping plans 0950
Indiana: Columbus: Industrial Medical Center / Landscaping plans 0874
Indiana: Columbus: Irwin Bank and Trust Company (Main Street) / Landscaping plans 0923
Indiana: Columbus: Irwin Union Bank & Trust Company / Landscaping plans 0607
Indiana: Columbus: Miller Residence / Landscaping plans 0396
Indiana: Columbus: Miller Townhouse / Landscaping plans 05020
Indiana: Columbus: North Christian Church / Landscaping plans 0608
Indiana: Columbus: North Elementary School / Landscaping plans 0610
Indiana: Columbus: Northside Middle School / Landscaping plans 01227
Indiana: Columbus: Occupational Health Center / Landscaping plans 0874
Indiana: Columbus: Otter Creek Clubhouse and Golf Course / Site plans 0593
Indiana: Columbus: Richards Elementary School / Landscaping plans 0610
Indiana: Columbus: Rte. 46 / Landscaping plans 0957
Indiana: Columbus: Schmitt Elementary School / Landscaping plans 01227
Indiana: Columbus: South Mapleton Building / Site plans 01037
Indiana: Darlington: Cummins Engine Company / Planting plans 0592
Indiana: Fort Wayne: Concordia College / Site plans 0707
Indiana: Fort Wayne: Concordia Theological Seminary / Master plans 0398
Indiana: Hanover: Hanover College / Landscaping plans 0847
Indiana: Indianapolis: Christian Theological Seminary / Preliminary drawings 0523
Indiana: Indianapolis: Cummins Engine Company / Landscaping plans 01077
Indiana: Madison: Cummins Engine Company Components Plant / Landscaping plans 01055
Indiana: North Wales: Cummins Engine Company / Landscaping plans 05041
Indiana: Taylorsville: Irwin Bank & Trust Company / Site plans 0878
Indiana: Walesboro: Cummins Engine Co. / Landscaping plans 01000
Iowa: Des Moines: Bucksbaum Residence / Site plans 01046
Iowa: Des Moines: Drake University / Master plans 0715
Japan: Osaka: Kansai International Airport / Schematic drawings 01193
Japan: Saitama: Saitama Super Arena / Landscaping plans 05035
Japan: Tokyo: Tokyo International Forum / Landscaping plans 01264
Jordan: Amman: United States Embassy / Competition drawings 01112
Kansas: Mission Hills: Hall Residence / Landscaping plans 01157
Kentucky: Frankfort: Justice & Law Complex / Master plans 01005
Louisiana: New Orleans: K & B Plaza / Landscaping plans 01054
Louisiana: Shreveport: Lillich Residence / Landscaping plans 01285
Maine: Carrabassett Vallett: Carrabassett Sugarloaf Development / Site plans 0872
Maine: Guilford / Master plans 0845
Maine: Kingfield: Sugarloaf Inn / Landscaping plans 0481
Maine: Kingfield: Sugarloaf Mountain Ski Lodge / Landscaping plans 0445
Maine: Piscataquis River / Master plans 0845
Maine: Rockport: Lewis Residence / Landscaping plans 01128
Maryland: Baltimore: Hooper House / Landscaping plans 0442
Maryland: Baltimore: Inner Harbor / Master plans 0913
Maryland: Bethesda: Seymour Krieger Residence / Landscaping plans 0436
Maryland: Butler: Bryan Residence / Landscaping plans 01120
Maryland: Potomac: Faith Trust / Landscaping plans 01110
Maryland: Rockville: Nuclear Use Systems / Master plans 01007
Massachusets: Hingham: Henry Stokes Residence / Landscaping plans 0363
Massachusetts: Andover: Laaff House / Landscaping plans 0444
Massachusetts: Belmont: McLean Hospital / Landscaping plans 0984
Massachusetts: Belmont: McLean Hospital / Site plans 0928
Massachusetts: Boston: Columbia Point: John F. Kennedy Presidential Library & Museum / Sketches 01003
Massachusetts: Boston: Faulkner Hospital / Landscaping plans 0979
Massachusetts: Boston: Franklin Park Zoo / Site plans 0730
Massachusetts: Boston: Pemberton Square / Landscaping plans 01160
Massachusetts: Boston: Post Office Square / Competition drawings 01176
Massachusetts: Boston: Stone & Webster / Landscaping plans 0947
Massachusetts: Cambridge: Elliott (James Barton) Residence / Planting plans 0560
Massachusetts: Hingham: Niles Residence / Landscaping plans 0512
Massachusetts: Hingham: Rudolph Talbot Residence / Landscaping plans 0205
Massachusetts: Jamaica Plain: Vila-Barret Residence / Landscaping plans 01154
Massachusetts: Manchester-by-the-Sea: Ross Residence / Architectural drawings 0856
Massachusetts: Mansfield: Wheaton College Library / Site plans 01022
Massachusetts: Martha's Vineyard: Michael Straight Residence / Landscaping plans 0511
Massachusetts: Medford: Tufts University / Landscaping plans 0788
Massachusetts: Medford: Tufts University / Master plans 0861